relationshiprewind.com 2018-10-15

# Relationship Rewind - Privacy Policy

Vin DiCarlo, Inc., Altare Publishing, Inc., and Mad Scientist Marketing, Ltd. (hereinafter collectively referred to as " **Altare** ")  are committed to respecting the privacy rights of users of the Website (all capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in Altare’s Terms of Service). Altare created this Privacy Policy to give You confidence as You visit and use the Website, and to demonstrate its commitment to fair information practices and to the protection of privacy.

This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Website and not to any websites of third parties (“ **Third-Party Websites** ”), which may have data collection, storage and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. For additional information, see the section concerning Third-Party Websites, below.  
BY USING THE WEBSITE, YOU REPRESENT AND WARRANT THAT YOU HAVE READ AND UNDERSTOOD, AND AGREE TO THE TERMS OF, THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT UNDERSTAND OR DO NOT AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU MUST IMMEDIATELY LEAVE THE WEBSITE.  
Each time You use the Website, the then-current version of this Privacy Policy will apply. Accordingly, each time You use the Website You should check the date of this Privacy Policy (which appears at the end) and review any changes since the last time You used the Website. For additional information, see the section concerning Updates and Changes to Privacy Policy, below.

###  1\. CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

BY USING THE WEBSITE OR SERVICES, YOU REPRESENT AND WARRANT THAT YOU ARE AT LEAST 18 YEARS OLD AND ARE OTHERWISE LEGALLY QUALIFIED TO ENTER INTO AND FORM CONTRACTS UNDER APPLICABLE LAW. 

Because all users of the Website are required to be at least 18 years of age, Altare does not solicit or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If Altare obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personally identifiable information from a child under the age of 13, Altare will immediately delete such information from its database. Because Altare does not collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, Altare has no such information to use or disclose to third parties. Altare has designed this Privacy Policy in order to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). 

### 2\. INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES 

**(a) Traffic Data.   **Like most website operators, Altare automatically gathers information of the sort that browsers automatically make available, including: (i) IP addresses; (ii) domain servers; (iii) types of computers accessing the Website; and (iv) types of Web browsers accessing the Website (collectively “ **Traffic Data** ”). Traffic Data is anonymous information that does not personally identify You.

**(b) Cookies.   **A “ **Cookie** ” is a string of information that a website stores on a user’s computer, and that the user’s browser provides to the website each time the user submits a query to the website. The purpose of a Cookie is to identify the user as a unique user of the Website. Altare uses Cookies to customize Your experience on the Website to Your interests, to ensure that You do not see the same advertisements or informational messages repeatedly, and to store Your password so You do not have to re-enter it each time You visit the Website. For additional information on Altare’s uses of Cookies, see the section concerning Information Use and Disclosure Practices/Traffic Data and Information Gathered Using Cookies, below. ****

IF YOU DO NOT WISH TO HAVE COOKIES PLACED ON YOUR COMPUTER, YOU SHOULD SET YOUR BROWSERS TO REFUSE COOKIES BEFORE ACCESSING THE WEBSITE, WITH THE UNDERSTANDING THAT CERTAIN OF THE SERVICES AND CERTAIN FEATURES OF THE WEBSITE MAY NOT FUNCTION PROPERLY WITHOUT THE AID OF COOKIES. IF YOU REFUSE COOKIES, YOU ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY RESULTING LOSS OF FUNCTIONALITY. 

**(c) Ad Serving.** Altare uses third-parties for advertising and analytics for pages that we host. These third-parties may place cookies on Your machine, use web beacons, gather IP addresses and log data to collect traffic and activity data to send to the United States in order to deliver relevant metrics, content, and advertising.  ****

**(d) Personal Information.   **In order for You to use certain of the Website services, You will be asked to provide Altare certain information that personally identifies You (“ **Personal Information** ”). Personal Information includes, without limitation: (1) “ **Contact Data** ” (such as Your e-mail address, website URLs, avatar URLs, and instant messaging screen names); and (2) **Demographic Data** ” (such as Your date of birth and gender). **** In each case, You will be asked to provide Personal Information; the Website will not gather it surreptitiously. Altare may supplement the Personal Information You provide with additional Personal Information gathered from public sources or from third-parties (e.g., consumer reporting agencies) who may lawfully provide such information to Altare.  ****

You are under no obligation to provide Personal Information, with the caveat that Your refusal to do so may prevent You from using certain of the Services.

**(e) Information You Make Public.** The Website contains features that permit You to upload, post, transmit, display, perform or distribute content, information or other, including Your Personal Information. Any information that You choose to disclose by means of such features becomes public information over which Altare is unable to exercise control. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose Your Personal Information by means of such features, and You agree to assume all responsibility for doing so.

### 3\. INFORMATION USE AND DISCLOSURE PRACTICES

**(a) Traffic Data and Information Gathered Using Cookies**

Altare analyzes Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies to help Altare better understand who is using the Website and how they are using it. By identifying patterns and trends in usage, Altare is able to better design the Website to improve Your experience, and to serve You more relevant and interesting content and advertisements.  From time to time, Altare may release Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies in the aggregate, such as by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the Website. Altare does not attempt to link information gathered using Cookies to Personal Information. ****

**(b) Personal Information**

**(i) Generally.   **Altare uses Your Contact Data to send You information about Altare and Altare’s products and services, and to contact You when necessary in connection with the Services. Altare uses Your Demographic Data to customize and tailor Your experience on the Website. As with Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies, from time to time Altare may release Demographic Data in the aggregate, such as by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the Website.  ****

**(ii) Disclosure Practices**

Altare will not share Your Personal Information except as comports with this Privacy Policy.  As Altare continues to develop, it may buy or sell subsidiaries or business units.  In such transactions, customer information is generally one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy.  At times, Altare may also share Your e-mail address with third parties so that they may notify you of special offers, products and services that may be of interest to You.  It is possible that Altare may rent, sell, or otherwise transfer Your Personal Information to such third parties.  At any time, You may contact Altare by email to [support@dicarlocoaching.com](mailto:support@dicarlocoaching.com) to request that Altare not share your Personal Information with third parties.  
Altare may also disclose Your Personal Information in the following circumstances:

  * **Disclosure in Connection with Services.  **Altare discloses Personal Information to those who help it provide services, including those who perform technical, administrative and data processing tasks such as ad serving, hosting, billing, fulfillment, and data storage and security. 

  * **By Law or to Protect Rights.**   Altare discloses Personal Information when required to do so by law, or in response to a subpoena or court order, or when Altare believes in its sole discretion that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Altare, third-parties or the public at large. 

  * **Business Transfers; Bankruptcy.**   Altare reserves the right to transfer all Personal Information in its possession to a successor organization in the event of a merger, acquisition, or bankruptcy or other sale of all or a portion of Altare’s assets.  Other than to the extent ordered by a bankruptcy or other court, the use and disclosure of all transferred Personal Information will be subject to this Privacy Policy, or to a new privacy policy if You are given notice of that new privacy policy and an opportunity to affirmatively opt-out of it.  Personal Information submitted or collected after a transfer, however, may be subject to a new privacy policy adopted by Altare’s successor organization. 

  * **License to User Content.** By using the Website, You grant the Altare Parties the right to publish Your name and any username of Yours in connection with the Altare Parties’ exercise of their license in and to Your User Content.  You further waive any claims arising from the Altare Parties’ exercise of that right. For additional information, see Terms of Service Section 15, regarding User Content.

### 4\. CONSENT TO RECEIVE EMAIL FROM ALTARE

By registering with the Website, you thereby consent to receive periodic email communications regarding the Services, new product offers, promotions and other matters. A simple 1-click unsubscribe link is included in each email, and by clicking on it You can unsubscribe at any time.

### 5\. SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Altare has implemented and maintains reasonable security procedures and practices to protect against the unauthorized access, use, modification, destruction or disclosure of Your Personal Information.   

### 6\. USER ABILITY TO ACCESS, UPDATE, AND CORRECT PERSONAL INFORMATION

Altare wants Your Personal Information to be complete and accurate. By using the Website, You represent and warrant that all information You provide on any registration form or otherwise in connection with Your use of the Website and Services will be complete and accurate, and that You will update that information as necessary to maintain its completeness and accuracy.  To confirm the completeness and accuracy of, or make changes to, Your Personal Information, please visit your account profile.

### 7\. PROMOTIONAL ACTIVITIES

From time to time, Altare may conduct contests, giveaways and other promotions (collectively, “ **Promotional Activities** ”). Any information submitted in connection with Promotional Activities will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy. From time to time, Altare may also ask You to participate in surveys designed to help Altare improve the Websites or Services. Any Personal Information provided to Altare in connection with any survey will be used only in relation to that survey, and will be disclosed to third parties not bound by this Privacy Policy only in aggregated form.

### 8\. UPDATES AND CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Altare reserves the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, update, change or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such update, change or modification on this page. Any such addition, update, change or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Website. Each time You use the Website, the then-current version of this Privacy Policy will apply. Accordingly, each time You use the Website You should check the date of this Privacy Policy (which appears at the end) and review any changes since the last time You used the Website. Unless Altare obtains Your express consent, any revised Privacy Policy will apply only to information collected after the effective date of such revised Privacy Policy, and not to information collected under any earlier Privacy Policy.

Effective Date: March 27, 2013

244 Fifth Ave, Suite 2311 New York, NY 10001  
1-800-563-4227
